<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Our Projects on Impact | Intelligent Marine Systems</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Our Projects on Impact | Intelligent Marine Systems</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2021 Impact. All Rights Reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tenth Coffee with EUMR</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-10/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-10/</guid><description>The EUMarineRobots (EUMR) project is glad to announce the tenth “Coffee with EUMR” webinar on Thursday, 24 June 2021 at 11:00 CET. This webinar will be hosted by the National Oceanography Centre (NOC) and will consist of two short talks presented by NOC.</description></item><item><title>Seventh Coffee with EUMR</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-7/</guid><description>The EUMarineRobots (EUMR) project is glad to announce the seventh “Coffee with EUMR” webinar on Thursday, 13 May 2021 at 10:30 CET. This webinar will be hosted by the University of Zagreb, Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computing (FER) and will consist of a short talk presented by FER and a short talk given by the Interuniversity Center of Integrated Systems for the Marine Environment (ISME).</description></item><item><title>Ninth Coffee with EUMR</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-9/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-9/</guid><description>The EUMarineRobots (EUMR) project is glad to announce the ninth “Coffee with EUMR” webinar on Thursday, 10 June 2021 at 11:00 CET. This webinar will be hosted by the University of Girona and will consist of two short talks presented by the University of Girona.</description></item><item><title>Eighth Coffee with EUMR</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-8/</guid><description>The EUMarineRobots (EUMR) project is glad to announce the eighth “Coffee with EUMR” webinar on Friday, 28 May 2021 at 11:00 CET. This webinar will be hosted by the Marine Institute and will consist of a short talk presented by the TNA end user Ulster University and a short talk given by the University of Limerick.</description></item><item><title>Sixth Coffee with EUMR</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-6/</guid><description>The EUMarineRobots (EUMR) project is glad to announce the sixth “Coffee with EUMR” webinar on Friday, 23 April 2021 at 10:30 CET. This webinar will be hosted by Norwegian University of Science and Technology (NTNU) and will consist of a short talk by NTNU and two short invited talks by end-users of TNAs performed at NATO STO CMRE.</description></item><item><title>Fifth Coffee with EUMR</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-5/</guid><description>The EUMarineRobots (EUMR) project is glad to announce the fifth “Coffee with EUMR” webinar on Friday, 9 April 2021 at 10:00 CET. This webinar will be hosted by Instituto Superior Técnico (IST-ID), University of Lisbon and will consist of a short talk by IST-ID and a short invited talk by the Indian Institute of Technology (IIT) Palakkad.</description></item><item><title>Fourth Coffee with EUMR</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-4/</guid><description>The EUMarineRobots (EUMR) project is glad to announce the fourth “Coffee with EUMR” webinar on Monday, 22 March 2021 at 11:00 CET. This webinar will be hosted by the National Research Council of Italy (CNR) Institute of Marine Engineering (INM) and will consist of a short talk by CNR-INM.</description></item><item><title>Third Coffee with EUMR</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-3/</guid><description>The EUMarineRobots (EUMR) project is glad to announce the third “Coffee with EUMR” webinar on Friday, 12 March 2021 at 14:30 CET. This webinar will be hosted by the AIR Centre and will consist of two short talks invited by the coordinator University of Porto in collaboration with the Swedish Maritime Robotics Centre (SMaRC).</description></item><item><title>Second Coffee with EUMR</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-2/</guid><description>The EUMarineRobots (EUMR) project is glad to announce the second “Coffee with EUMR” webinar on Wednesday, 24 February 2021 at 11 AM CET. The second webinar will be hosted by PLOCAN and will consist of two short talks by invited PLOCAN collaborators.</description></item><item><title>First Coffee with EUMR</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/coffee-with-eumr-1/</guid><description>The EUMarineRobots (EUMR) project is glad to announce the series of webinars “Coffee with EUMR” starting in February! These webinars will present the best of the research performed within the scope of EUMR and related initiatives.</description></item><item><title>BREAKING THE SURFACE 2019</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/bts-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/bts-2019/</guid><description>What is BTS? BTS is a summer workshop that encourages interaction and the exchange of knowledge and experience about the field of maritime robotics and its applications
Why attend?</description></item><item><title>BREAKING THE SURFACE 2020</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/bts-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/bts-2020/</guid><description>Visit the lectures
What is BTS? BTS is a summer workshop that encourages interaction and the exchange of knowledge and experience about the field of maritime robotics and its applications</description></item><item><title>BREAKING THE SURFACE 2021</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/bts-2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/bts-2021/</guid><description>What is BTS? BTS is a summer workshop that encourages interaction and the exchange of knowledge and experience about the field of maritime robotics and its applications
Why attend?</description></item><item><title>Example Project</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/_example/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/_example/</guid><description>After copying this file or its content and adjusting the front matter above, everything below this line (and this line aswell) can be deleted and replaced with the content of the project page.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Venture Capital</title><link>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/understanding-venture-capital/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://impact.uni-bremen.de/projects/understanding-venture-capital/</guid><description>Description For most startups, raising an investment is the holy grail of their development. However - is venture capital also the right path for your startup? Very often, startups enter investment discussions without an understanding of how investors think and what guides their decisions.</description></item></channel></rss>